General Ning is here.
What did you call me?
General Ning.
General Ning has always
looked down on
these entertainment houses.
What brings you here today?
I suspect the person who fought Cui Hu
at the Qixi Lantern Festival
is an enemy spy
from the Northern Frontier.
This person is currently
hiding in the city.
You are the manager here.
You should know.
Make sure no thieves sneak in.
Otherwise,
you can't bear
the crime of harboring spies.
I appreciate your kind reminder, General.
General Ning,
Mr. Chu
is very responsible.
He is in charge of the renovation of
the whole theater.
He truly deserves to be called
the greatest talent in the capital.
Hanging his painting
up makes
the whole place shine,
doesn't it?
Rule number one of
advancing a relationship:
the best way to make
a man realize his feelings
is to make him jealous first.
Ning Yuanci is extremely possessive.
He likes women who take the initiative,
but not too much.
Watch how I play hard to get with him.
General Ning,
my father said your marriage to my sister
is a done deal.
Even with your high status,
there's nothing you can do.
So Ying'er won't blame you.
After you marry my sister,
we can still be friends.
You must come visit
our theater in the future.
Mr. Chu and I
will definitely treat you well.
I, Ning Yuanci,
never make friends with women.
I think you just don't
have any friends at all.
At the engagement party,
you only had Cui Hu with you.
Five years ago
General Ning's father, Marquis Zhongjing,
was ambushed by the Northern Army.
His brothers and parents
all sacrificed their lives in that battle.
Now,
he is indeed the only one
left in the Ning family.
That's so tragic.
The Duke and Marquis Zhongjing
had been best friends since their youth.
Lady Keying,
I can't believe you didn't know...
Xue Shiyan thinks
Xue Ruowan's marriage to me
is a foregone conclusion.
But this matter is not for him to decide.
Deliver the marriage document I prepared
to the Duke's Residence.
Xue Keying and I are deeply in love.
Today I will petition His Majesty
for a new marriage decree.
Ning Yuanci is going to marry Ying'er.
My Ying'er has finally gotten her wish.
Look.
This is wonderful news.
I do not agree.
How can Ning Yuanci
just pick and choose
which of my daughters to marry?
You...
How does this handwriting look?
Last time, Keying said
she wanted to change the theater's plaque.
She asked me to write it
and have it framed.
My Lady,
for so many years in the mansion,
the Second Young Lady has bullied
and made things difficult for you.
She snatches away
everything you like.
Yet you still help her like this.
Xiaolan,
people can't always live in the past,
let alone live in hatred.
Although Keying is unruly,
she is not bad by nature.
Besides, even if someone makes a mistake,
everyone deserves
a chance to be forgiven.
If Xiaolan makes a mistake,
will you forgive me, My Lady?
Of course.
We grew up together
like sisters.
I have
something to tell you.
I,
Xue Ruowan,
Ning Yuanci is preparing
to request an imperial decree.
Have His Majesty revoke
your marriage contract with him.
Really?
Yes, really.
Truly.
But will Father agree?
Father is most afraid of offending people.
Ning Yuanci is the Defender General.
He is also His Majesty's adopted son.
How could Father go against him?
It is so hot.
I came to tell you this good news
the moment I heard it.
Your scar
seems to have faded a bit.
It seems so.
Maybe it's because I've been
in a good mood lately,
so my skin got firmer.
By the way,
I've finished the calligraphy
you asked for last time.
What beautiful handwriting.
Once your engagement is broken off,
you'll be completely free.
Then you can focus on your career
with Mr. Chu.
An ambitious princess,
to achieve military merits,
Disguising her identity
to approach the innocent and kind
tribal prince,
the two fell in love amidst a deception.
The princess's scheme
led to the annihilation
of the prince's entire tribe.
Agonized by his love for the princess,
he decided to jump
into the River of Amnesia.
Filled with endless regret,
the princess
jumped down with him.
After waking up...
They lost their memories,
met again,
and fell back in love,
starting
a bittersweet romance of reuniting.
What do you think?
It's okay.
It's fine if you don't understand.
Anyway, you play the princess,
and you play the tribal prince.
I can't act in this play.
Since a princess can achieve
military merits,
why not
just stage
Mulan taking her father's place
in the army?
Classic plays are good,
but without
a dramatic romance,
the audience won't buy it.
Let's perform this
for our opening premiere.
After Amnesia.
And falling in love with the enemy,
the prince.
Isn't that a bit too tragic?
Can't you see
I am helping you?
There is no
better opportunity than falling in love
through acting.
Keying,
are you hiding something
from me?
Well...
I plan to leave the theater
after the premiere.
You two
manage it well together.
Leave?
Why is that?
Because
I am going to marry Ning Yuanci.
What?
You are marrying Ning Yuanci?
Yes.
Why else do you think
he suddenly
broke off the engagement?
But you know full well
his marriage alliance with the Xue family
is only for power.
You also said
you no longer like him.
Why still marry him?
Life is like a play.
If he can deceive,
so can I.
Besides,
one of us
has to marry him.
As for you,
go live the life you want
and love the one you want to love.
As for Ning Yuanci,
leave him to me to deal with.
You were the one
who proposed building this theater.
Now you are going back on your word
and leaving.
Then I quit too.
I am doing this all for your own good.
I never asked you
to do all this for me.
Besides,
when you did it,
did you ever ask
if I actually needed it?
I...
Ladies,
please don't argue
over such a small thing.
Don't be mad.
None of your business.
Are you still angry?
Please accept my apology.
I take back what I said
about leaving the troupe.
I just wanted
to give you and Young Master Chu
more chances
to be alone.
Young Master Chu and I
are merely friends.
Why must you
insist on playing matchmaker for us?
I agreed
to run Moxiang Theater with you
because you said that
even as women of the inner courtyard,
we have the right
to pursue freedom
and dreams.
Besides,
I don't want you
to accept a loveless marriage
for my sake.
Okay, okay,
I know you're a strong independent woman.
You have no room
for romance in your head.
Although I agreed to the engagement
mainly to help you,
Ning Yuanci and I
aren't completely devoid of true feelings.
It wouldn't hurt to have
a little romance.
Ning Yuanci did ask the Emperor
for a new marriage edict,
but Father went to
the Privy Council early this morning
to submit a memorial.
He claimed General Ning abandoned you
and tried to ruin
the reputation of us sisters,
asking the Emperor
to uphold the original engagement.
What?
Why is Father ruining my plans too?
It just shows how much
Father truly cares for you.
He can't bear to see you
enter the General's Manor,
that lion's den.
But Ning Yuanci...
It's not that scary, is it?
Rumor has it that
General Ning is ruthless
and debauched.
He often tortures and kills
the maids in his mansion,
and to women, he is even...
Rumors stop with the wise.
Not even a female mosquito
can get into
his backyard.
Even if Father stands in my way,
I have a plan.
What plan?
The trick of a substitute bride
may be cliché,
but it always works.
The world calls her a phoenix
on the branch,
a woman favored by fate.
No one knows she is
but a sparrow in the palm,
at the mercy of fate at every turn.
If the phoenix does not rise
from the ashes...
can only be reduced
to a plaything for others to admire.
Though the sparrow is small,
it has the courage
to break free from its shackles.
You are me,
and I am you.
General,
what play are they performing?
I have never seen it before.
Either a sparrow becomes a phoenix,
or a phoenix becomes a sparrow.
General Ning has a sharp eye.
Guess who is the older sister
and who is the younger.